a girl on Independence Day came out in a
девушка на День Независимости вышла в
Ukrainian embroidered shirt, she was arrested, so there is
украинской вышиванке арестовали её так
such a thing. Do you agree that once
есть такое есть Вы согласны что лю ещё
again the people who in Crimea declare
раз люди которые в Крыму декларируют
their pro-un position They are being persecuted, they
свою проун скую позицию Они преследуются
agree, depending on what they
согласны смотря что они
say
говорят
about hello Andrey o Everything, I
о здравствуйте Андрей о Всё я вас
remembered you Yes, it’s just that you are seriously without headphones
вспомнил Да просто вы без наушников
Yes yes we are talking about uh You are now either from the
серьёзно Да да мы про э Вы сейчас либо с
Belgorod region not not from the
Белгородской области не не с
Belgorod region And from the Bryansk
Белгородской А с Брянской
region no no well, in short, you and I are
области нет нет ну короче мы с вами то
either Voronezh Yes, somewhere nearby We
или Воронеж Да где-то рядом Мы с вами
talked for a long time there literally an hour and an hour and an
долго общались там буквально час да час
hour we talked, I remember And how  you remember
час общались я помню А как вы помните
me amazingly Well, you were in the light and
меня удивительно Ну вы При свете были и
without headphones Well, I remembered from his face
без науш Ну по лицу
I’m just not a memorable
вспомнил я просто не запоминающийся
person, even Even even twice We seemed to
персона даже Даже даже два раза Мы вроде
have talked once for a long time and the second time
один раз Долго общались а второй раз
It seemed like that Tui ti No I
Вроде так Туй ти Нет я
Well, we met well, like so
Ну встретились ну типа
seriously then one  since
так чтоб серьёзно то один раз очень
we talked there for a very long time, I remember your position, yes,
долго мы там общались помню вашу позицию
it’s a long one. And what is my position, well, it’s
да са долгий А какая у меня позиция ну
like it’s not for the war and it’s like, and
такая она как бы и не за войну и типа и
it’s unclear, I have an even shorter bunch of
непонятно у меня ещё короче куча
subscribers Yes, he’s not Normal,
подписчиков Да не он Нормальный
normal, something loaded him there like it’s not
нормальный что-то его там грузил типа не
me  I remember, you know, I talked to you and
я помню знаете я вот мы с вами
then I went to Stream and
пообщались потом Я перешёл на Стрим и
watched our conversation and then
посмотрел нашу вот эту общение и потом
you said, like, Oh, that’s okay.
вы сказали типа О ну нормально такой
We talked normally. You kind of
Нормально пообщались Типа вы как как бы
said, well, plus or minus, I’m a normal
сказали ну плюс-минус я нормальный
person, let’s say you can communicate with me,
человек скажем так со мной можно
well.  didn’t communicate communicated at
общаться ну не общались общались У вас у
your place I remember you didn’t have some kind of
вас Я помню у вас не было какой-то там
like And there was a beti Khokhlo and so on Yes, but it’s
типа А там бети хохло и так дальше Да но
kind of unclear but in you and I we talked
как бы непонятно а во мы с вами общались
like are you to blame for this and like and you
типа виноваты ли вы в этом да типа и вы
kind of pull away like  I have nothing to do with it at all,
как бы отстраняется типа я тут вообще ни
like, yes, like, we Citizens of
при чём типа да типа мы Граждане
the Russian Federation are not to blame, and in
Российской Федерации не виноваты да в
this war, like, we actually discussed a lot of
этой войне типа мы на самом деле много
topics, so
тем обсудили поэтому
Oh, and this is in your Voronezh region, yes,
Ой а это у вас в Воронежской области же
Petropavlovka flew to the village, yes,
да в село это Петропавловка прилетела да
yes, I don’t know when there today  - Yes, I don’t
да сегодня там не знаю когда-то Да я не
know, it’s us, you, no, look, Swa
знаю это мы вы так нет смотри Сва
first said that Ukraine was
сначала сказала что Украина это ж ваши
already recognized by your governor, but yours said I do
уже признали губернатор же ваш сказал Я
n’t even know about Skabeeva, I’m talking about our
про я даже скабееву не знаю я про нашего
governor, like the governor
губернатора говорю типа губернатор
said that there was an emergency drop from a
сказал что вот аварийный сброс из
bomber Yes, it hit me  but again,
бомбардировщика Да попал вот но опять же
there is no Truth and I don’t know. Well, why does
Правды то нет и не знаю Ну а зачем
your governor need
вашему губернатору
to lie? Well, if he says that
брехать Ну если он скажет что типа это
like you did it, then
вы типа сделали то это его
Belgorod will tear him apart, in short, they’ll iron it
порвёт Белгород короче утюжат
and you’re just glad, so glad, honestly, yes,
а Вы прям рады такие рады рады честно да
I’m glad, look, I’m glad because A
я рады вот смотрите я рады потому что А
we are not happy I will explain, look Why
мы не рады я объясню смотрите Почему
Because the difference We are the victim you are the aggressor
Потому что разница Мы жертва вы агрессор
therefore the
поэтому
damage to the aggressor Yes it’s cool we didn’t attack
урон агрессору Да это круто не мы напали
you that’s why When Russia bombs
на вас поэтому Когда Россия бомбит
Ukrainian cities It’s bad when
украинские города Это плохо когда
Ukraine strikes back It’s
Украина наносит удары в ответ Это
good I’ll ask you one question like this
хорошо я вам задам один вопрос такой
Elementary a little historically  yes What do
Элементарно немножко исторически да Как
you think the Soviet Union when it invaded the
вы считаете Советский Союз когда вторгся
territory of Germany Is this the right
на территории Германии Это правильное
decision or
решение либо
no not the Soviet Union on the territory of
нет не Советский Союз на территории
Germany look
Германии смотри
d look Germany attacked the Soviet
г смотри Германия напала на Советский
Union Yes Germany was the aggressor
Союз Да Германия была агрессором
The Soviet Union in this scheme was the victim
Советский Союз в этой схеме был жертвой
Yes that’s why the Soviet Union defended itself
Да вот поэтому Советский Союз защищался
Yes no in  soro che Mado he liberated his
Да нет в соро че Мадо он освободил свои
lands and his aggressor yes, that is,
земли так и своего агрессора да то есть
he destroyed his aggressor Absolutely
он уничтожал своего агрессора Абсолютно
true Yes That is, he liberated his lands
верно Да То есть он освободил свои земли
and went Absolutely true Yes To
и пошёл Абсолютно верно Да Чтобы
destroy That’s what he did correctly yes
уничтожить Вот это правильно сделал да
together with his allies Yes USA Britain so
вместе с союзниками Да США Британия так
Far
Дале
what was the goal  not also Look,
какая была цель не также Смотри вот а
look, absolutely absolutely, too,
смотри абсолютно абсолютно тоже тут
it will be here, yes, Russia attacked Ukraine, Yes,
будет да Россия напала на Украину Да
Ukraine, Yes, together with its allies, Britain,
Украина Да вместе с союзниками Британия
as well as against the Third Reich, Britain, USA,
как и против третьего рейха Британия США
and so on, Yes, it will liberate Ukraine Yes, and yes, yes, yes, it
и так дальше Да освободит Украину Да и э
will go to Moscow, Yes, it will dismember the
за Да пойдёт до Москвы Да расчленить
Russian Federation.  Let's talk about
Российскую Федерацию Да а вот Давайте по
this.
этой
Victory for Ukraine will be that the
поговорим Победа Украина будет что цель
goal of the Victory of Ukraine is the withdrawal of
цель Победы Украины - это отвод войск
Russian troops to the borders of the ninety-first year,
России до границ девяносто перго года
the day of the first year yes yes The first one will be Yes,
дено перго года да да Первое это будет
I understand, let's talk about an example about
Да я понял давайте поговорим пример про
Crimea as you see, that is, the military
Крым так как вы видите то есть военная
base that is now there  is
база которая сейчас там находится
Russian, it will remain there Or you will
Российская она там останется Либо вы её
destroy it, of course it won’t remain Well,
уничтожит конечно не останется Ну
look, some will float away,
смотри часть часть уплывёт часть убежит
some will run away, some will be more politely stunned to write
часть будет важливе оголошення пишиться
on Tsei’s reserve channel Andr popk
на Цей резервный канал Андр попк
chatroulette there every day there will be
чатрулетка там кожен день будуть выходи
new and new videos where and everything is how you
новы и новые видео куда да и всё как вы
do it by force  so
это сделаете насильственным путём так
no by force they all
никакого насильственным путём сами все
fled from Kherson Well, it’s not their
как с Херсона убежали Ну они не это их
native land, what will they do? They’ll really
родная земля что они сделают вот реально
want to leave,
захотят уезжать
look, it’s very simple, yes. That means
смотрите очень просто да Значит
Russian troops are leaving Crimea,
российские войска уходят из Крыма
Donetsk and Lugansk, and those who clearly
Донецка и Луганска да те кто явно
collaborated with the occupation authorities. Yes,
сотрудничал с оккупационной властью Да
they will be the first to flee.  ranks Yes people
они побегут в первых рядах Да люди
who Yes people who will not want to
которые Да люди которые не захотят
leave Yes they remain yes those who
Уезжать Да они остаются да те которые
came uh after the 2014 occupation from
приехали ээ после оккупации 2014 года из
Russia will be deported to Russia and
России будут депортированы в Россию да
those who were citizens of Ukraine in 2014
те которые были в 2014 гражданам Украины
Yes and will not want to leave for the Russian
Да и не захотят уехать в Российскую
Federation Yes they will filter out
Федерацию Да будут профильтровать
cooperation with the occupation  authorities
сотрудничества с оккупационной властью
cooperate with participation in murders or
сотрудни участия в убийствах или
persecution of the population Yes, if everything is
преследования ээ населения Да если всё
normal, a person lives Yes Like if how
нормально человек живёт Да Типа если как
you do it from a legal point
вы это сделаете с юридической точки
of view How you do it there Millions of
зрения Как вы сделаете там Миллионы
people through the court will be through the court yes yes
людей через суд будет через суд будет да
investigation Yes look, investigations are being done
да следствие Да смотри делаются
as they did for example in this  100
следствен как сделал например в это 100
years you will make 100 years old 100 years
лет будете делать 100 леткой 100лет
Look, there
Смотри вот
were initially so few people in Kherson,
людей в Херсоне было изначально сколько
in fact, look stop
немного на самом деле так смотри стоп
stop they drew a referendum
стоп нарисовали по референдуму
they drew 99% of support there Well Crimea is a
нарисовали там 99% поддержки Ну Крым это
completely different Crimea after once
абсолютно другая Крыму после ещ раз ещё
again look at the
раз смотри
drawn numbers exactly the same as in
нарисованные цифры точно такие же как в
Crimea with what No you were in Crimea in what
Крыму де с чем Нет вы были в Крыму в чем
year or after in rinat year after of
году или после в ринатом году бы после
course you wouldn’t No after the fourteenth
конечно не был Нет после четырнадцатого
year you wouldn’t be after what of course yes That
года вы бы после че не был конечно да То
is, you don’t know
есть вы не знаете
that I I know that ordinary people who For
что я я знаю что обычные люди которы Вот
example, we  watch the news Yes, people sing
например мы смотрим новости Да люди поют
Verka Serduchka they say Glory to Ukraine and the
Верку Сердючку говорят Слава Украине и к
FSB breaks in on them and that’s why people in Crimea
ним врывается ФСБ и поэтому люди в Крыму
You agree, they cannot voice their
Вы согласны не могут озвучить свою
real position,
настоящую позицию
they agree, we sing songs in Ukrainian in the
согласны у нас на украинском языке поют
federal language, look again
песни на федеральных кана ещё раз смотри
You agree Let’s agree that in
Вы согласны Давай со согласны что в
Crimea  Yes, come on, there is a channel called the
Крыму Да вот Зайдите есть канал такой
Crimean SMERSH, they are directly catching
Крымский СМЕРШ они прямо отлавливает
everyone who somewhere has expressed at least some kind of
всех кто где-то высказал хоть какую-то
Ukrainian position, a girl on
украинскую позицию девушка на День
Independence Day came out in a Ukrainian
Независимости вышла в в украинской
embroidered shirt, they arrested her, so there is such a thing.
вышиванке арестовали её так есть такое
Do you agree that people are once again people
есть Вы согласны что люди ещё раз люди
who in Crimea declare their  pro-
которые в Крыму декларируют свою проун
un position They are being persecuted, they
скую позицию Они преследуются
agree, depending on what they say Let's
согласны смотря что они говорят Давайте
decide What they say if they
определимся Что они говорят если они
say something like A they support you and the
говорят типа А вас поддерживают а
Russian occupiers there need to
российские там оккупанты их нужно
destroy them and the Russians stop stop
уничтожать и русски ещё раз стоп стоп
stop look again Wait, you say yes what
стоп смотри Подожди вы говорите да что
no If a person is for Ukraine Yes they will close
нет Если человек за Украину Да закроют
what  that is, people you are now talking about
что то есть людей вы сейчас говорите
people who say that Russia is an
людей которые говорят что Россия
occupier, they will be closed.
оккупант их закроют
Yes, no, it depends on what is needed. And
Да нет смотря нужно А ещё раз ещё раз
look again, let’s see what will happen. This is what will happen
смотри давай так что будет Вот что будет
and a certain situation if a person
да определённая ситуация если человек
now in Yalta says that Russia is an occupier,
сейчас в Ялте скажет что Россия оккупант
what
что с ним
will happen to him, the court will
будет суд
decide stop  that is, a person who,
решит стоп то есть человек который
wait again, a person who
подожди ещё раз человек который
was a citizen of Ukraine, yes, and he believes
гражданин Украины был да и он считает
that Russia, the occupier, will judge him.
что Россия оккупант его будут судить
No, he won’t be judged if they find him,
Нет его не бут судить если найдут
look, if they find a connection that he
смотрите если найдут связь что он
supported ZSU, look again,
поддерживал зсу ещё раз ещё раз смотри
man, he is a
человек е
man, that is, look, come on  so
раз человек то есть смотри давай так
if a person simply says, for example,
человек если просто скажет например всё
look at everything, I’ll explain, it means look, in short,
смотри те объясняю значит Смотри короче
all this means don’t look, I’ll
всё это значит не смотри я тебе оче
give it to you, so that we put an end to this, all the
давай так чтобы мы поставили на это
inhabitants of the Crimean peninsula who
все жители Крымского полуострова которые
arrived after what year deteriorated
приехали после чего года де портится
back who was there before what year, if they themselves did not
назад кто был до чего года если сами не
run away  Yes, who supported Russia, yes,
убежали Да кто поддерживал Россию да Во
filtration will be carried out for 10,000
будут проведены фильтрационные за 10.000
100,000 of all
100 000 всех
In short, not a million No, there is a
Короче не миллиона Нет там там
majority there Supports you again,
большинство Поддерживает у ещё раз
look at a million Okay, let’s do that, a million
смотри миллион Хорошо давай так миллион
Everyone everyone who supported the
Все каждый каждая которая поддерживала
occupation regime will
оккупационный режим будет
go Yes and pull
дут Да и притянуть
the answer, look if the person supports
отве смотри если человек поддерживает
the Russian  Federation occupation regime
Российскую Федерацию оккупационный режим
once again No no need to take turns no no no
ещё раз Нет не надо по очереди нет не
need to take turns once again because we
надо по очереди ещё раз потому что мы
put an end to this we also put an end to this
ставим этом точку ещё мы ставим в этом
I’m a blogger that’s why you’re listening to me
точку Я блогер поэтому ты меня слушаешь
let’s now look we put an end to the question
давай теперь смотри ставим точку вопрос
the person who will support the occupation
человек который поддержит оккупационную
power he do you agree that  who
власть он ты согласен что кто
supports the occupation power he no
поддерживает оккупационную власть он нет
Well, that all means what you and I are going to
Ну всё значит о чём мы с тобой будем
talk about look again what we are going to
говорить смотри ещё раз о чём мы будем
talk about is a person who will support the
говорить человек который поддержит
occupation
оккупационную
power if Human E times look a person
власть если Челове е раз смотри человек
who is not a person who supports
который нет человек который поддерживает
the occupation this is the base this is the base
оккупационную это базовая это база
Look this is not a position not  if you want, come on
Смотри это не позиция не хоче е давай
Glasha, that the person who will support the
Глаша что человек который поддержит
occupation
оккупационную
power is the one who interrupts me,
власть перева я тебя ты меня перебиваешь
don’t interrupt me when I interrupt,
не пере меня когда перебиваю я
Pony That’s because I’m a blogger, you understand,
Поня Вот потому что я блогер понимаешь
you’re silent And you’re listening to me now,
ты молчишь И слушаешь меня теперь
look in general What kind of culture of communication
смотри обще Какая культура общения
look if a
смотри если
person Look, you’re talking Yes, and about the
человек Смотри говоришь Да и про
culture of communication  will you tell me
культуру общения будешь мне рассказывать
so shut up now look if a person
так помолчи тепер смотри если человек
denies
отрицает
the occupation power What to talk about this
оккупационную власть О чём говорить это
is
есть
the base Yes, just like people who in Russia
база Да также как люди которые в России
there are people who do not support our
есть люди которые не поддерживают нашу
power people
власть люди
who in the occupation in the
которые на оккупационных на
occupied territories support
оккупированных территориях поддерживают
Yes Russia, that is, the occupation power
Да Россию то есть оккупационную власть
they Base base you  against democracy
они База база ты против демократии
I understand you correctly No, this is not
правильно тебя понима Нет это не
democracy,
демократия
look No, this is not
смотри Нет это не
democracy In short, look Let me
демократия Короче смотри Давай так я
turn off the sound for you
тебе отключаю звук
now before I tell you, I turned down
сейчас до говорю я тебе скрутил немножко
the sound a little Yes, so that you mean Look,
звук Да чтобы ты значит Смотри
that's because democracy is
ты Вот потому что демократия - это
never, for example, Russia Yes, this is an
никогда например Россия Да это
insult,
оскорбление
you three  times insulted, look, democracy
ты три раза оскорбил смотри демократия
is never the occupation power
это никогда оккупационная власть
comes and says You must respect
приходит и говорит Вы должны уважать
our occupation power, this is democracy
нашу оккупационную власть это демократия
Yes, when the Third Reich seized
Да когда Третий рейх захватывал
territories Yes, this is not democracy, this is
территории Да это не демократия это
occupation When Russia captured Lugansk
оккупация Когда Россия захватила Луганск
Donetsk Crimea, the Kherson part of the Zaporozhye
Донецк Крым херсонскую часть Запорожская
part of the region Yes, this is not democracy Yes,
часть области Да это не демократия Да
this is violent  occupation Yes and
вот это насильственная оккупация Да и
therefore the base Those who cooperate with the
поэтому база Кто сотрудничает с
occupation authorities are those
оккупационные властями те
Yes who in Crimea collaborated with the
Да которая в Крыму сотрудничала с
occupation authorities will be held
оккупационной властью будет привлечена к
accountable yes until the moment the ZSU enters
ответственности да до момента входа зсу
Crimea there will be an opportunity to escape through the
в Крым будет возможность убежать через
Crimean bridge into the water no matter everyone who
Крымский мост в плав неважно все кто
collaborated please Flee away like from
сотрудничал пожалуйста Утекай как с
Kherson Yes the Stremousovs escaped  ran away
Херсона Да убежали стремоусовы убежали
Yes, for example, they will run away who will not run away
Да например вот убегут кто не убежит
please
пожалуйста
everyone who collaborated with the tion
будете все кто сотрудничал с ционной
authorities supported the military
властью поддерживал
military Russian
военные военных российских
law enforcement agencies Russian
правоохранительные органы российские
who persecuted Ukrainian citizens
которые преследовали украинских граждан
yes you will be in prison all come on
да будете сидеть в тюрьме всё давай
Glory to
Слава
Ukraine that bazaars are known
Украине что базары это з ным
Yes if a person yes put a plus who
Да если человек да поставьте плюс кто
agrees with  me yes put plus who
согласен со мной да поставьте плюс кто
agrees with me if a person starts to
согласен со мной если человек начинает
fornicate This is the word And you are against
Вот это слово блудить А ты против
democracy Yes
демократии Да
and denies that those who uh collaborate with the
и отрицает что те кто ээ сотрудничает с
occupation authorities yes What to
оккупационные властями да О чём дальше
talk about next is the base is a new channel Write to Nyogo
говорить это база це новый канал Пиши на
right away Put the dialer on so you can turn it
нього прямо зараз Постав дзвоник щоб
off  fistula we'll be on the link
отримати ус свище будем на звязку
and stunned pi on Tsey reserve channel
ж оголошення ппи на Цей резервний канал
Andr Popik chatroulette I created another
Андр Попик чатрулетка я створив ще один
channel on some vikladav unique video I did
канал на який викладав уникальни вдео я
n't Buli on this channel nor on streams
не Були на цьому канали ни на стримах
write on a new day there every day they will
пишиться на нього там кожен день будуть
come out but and but video squeak comment
виходити но и но вдео писка комент
skin video  YouTube is effective,
кожным видео щоб YouTube ефективни прова
we will collapse that channel so that more
мы пон рухну той канал для то щоб бильше
people can extract information from our videos, that's
людей отримували информацию з наших вдео
what our channel Yes, a little bit of YouTube,
тому що це Наш канал Да трошки YouTube
having driven the new banh mi, we will try in parallel
загнав ньй бан ми будем пробу паралельно
with the writing
ро он пись